Robert Johnson

Full Stack Engineer

CONTACT



320-630-0721



Robertejohnson10@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/robert-johnson-323bb2aa



github.com/RobertEJohnson

EDUCATION

Full Stack Software Engineering Certification

Prime Digital Academy, MN || May 2020 - September 2020

Bachelor's || Communication **Studies / Theatre Generalist**

St. Cloud State University, MN || 2012-2016

SKILLS

- React
- Redux
- JavaScript
- Python3
- Flask
- Node
- Express
- PostgreSQL
- jQuery
- CSS3 | HTML5
- Material-UI
- Bootstrap

PROFILE

Inspired and innovative engineer who has a wealth of experience working with small and international businesses. Bolstered by a wellpracticed background in communication, customer service and the performative arts. A calculated self-learner who is not afraid to improvise solutions and adapt frequently. Somewhat obsessed with self-improvement, videogame development, and cats.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PinDo – Lead Application Developer

Remote | August 2020 - Present

- Established a web-based project tack board which rectifies common restraints with existing project boards through providing high degrees of user freedom and layout restructuring capacity.
- Utilized technologies such as React, Redux, Node, Express, PostgreSQL, Material-UI, Passport, Bcrypt, React-Router.

Prime Digital Academy - Full Stack Engineering Student Remote | May 2020 - Present

- Full-time immersive full-stack stack work.
- Created multitudes of projects independently or with groups of engineers with various modern technologies and frameworks.
- Cultural diversity and inclusion trained.

Carl Zeiss Vision - Operator

St. Cloud, MN | August 2019 – March 2020

- Operated on the lowest staffed to highest output shift.
- Operated in a highly dynamic and dangerous work environment.
- Go-to employee to learn new machines and adapt to various roles.
- Recommended to and worked with onboarding new employees.

Paramount Center for the Arts - Stage Technician / Stage Manager St. Cloud, MN | May 2019 - Nov 2019

- Operated technical equipment live for performances and events.
- Maintained various delicate and expensive theatre equipment.
- Head of communications between performers, technical staff, and front of house staff throughout live performances.
- Kept time-sensitive operations timely and was one of the primary sources for handling unexpected events.